

GAME PROGRAMMER

### **Details**

Gdańsk

Poland

grzpotry@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Polish

DATE OF BIRTH

1995

#### Links

LinkedIn

**Github** 

#### **Skills**

Unreal Engine / C++

Unity / C#

**Gameplay Programming** 

Networking code

Continous Integration

Performance Optimizations

Git / Perforce

**Editor tools** 

Al - Behaviour Trees & State machines

**Procedural Generation** 

# Languages

Polish (native)

English (fluent)

# **Profile**

Over 8 years of experience in game software development as a programmer. In total 8 years in Unity and 2 years in Unreal Engine on which I am recently mostly focused on.

With a wealth of experience in transforming design concepts into gameplay, I thrive when tackling new challenges and realizing ambitious visions.

Consider myself as generalist - extensive experience in a rapidly growing studio required wearing many hats and engaging in various phases of the production, from concept, through rough development - to the final releases and product maintenance.

# **Employment History**

### Unreal Engine Programmer - TPP Action rpg project, Event Horizon

JANUARY 2024 - PRESENT

As the most experienced team member in the Unreal ecosystem, I led the development of a new project on Unreal Engine 5.3, focusing on creating a vertical slice for a TPP Action RPG roguelike game centered around combat. My responsibilities included establishing an efficient development environment for the team and developing core features of the early prototype. Key contributions involved:

- Customizing the Lyra Sample project for our specific needs, enabling easy reuse and extension of existing systems, and configuring version control for the repository.
- Leveraging Modular Game Features to maintain a clean separation between core Lyra foundations and our custom game logic.
- Establishing unified standards eg. for using GAS across the whole team.
- Setting up CI pipelines for automated builds and tests in TeamCity.
- Developing core combat mechanics, including melee attacks, movement with motion warping, basic enemy AI, player skills & controls, and essential application features such as saving and interaction systems.

### Senior Unity Programmer - Dark Envoy, Event Horizon

OCTOBER 2018 - JANUARY 2024

#### PC Release in 10/2023

https://store.steampowered.com/app/945770/Dark Envoy/

Served as a Senior Programmer, overseeing the entire project lifecycle from initial conceptualization to full release and ongoing post-release maintenance. Led the development of key project areas, primarily focusing on gameplay systems programming, while also enhancing team efficiency by developing editor tools and maintaining the repository and Continuous Integration servers.

Additionally, for two years, I supervised the content scripting team, effectively planning their tasks and providing necessary technical support. This responsibility was managed alongside my other programming duties, ensuring seamless project progression.

Chief technical areas of expertise in this project

- Developed Procedural Content Generation systems (dungeons, loot, quests etc.)
- Leaded enemies AI development, prepared BT tools used by designers
- Integrated and supervised 3rd party tools (eg. visual scripting) for designers

### **Hobbies**

Science, Astrophysics, Outdoor, Scuba-Diving, Hiking, Videography, Triathlon, Sci-Fi

- Collaborated on core combat and quests mechanics
- Supported development of multiplayer features
- Automated build, and testing pipelines by utilizing CI system (jenkins)
- Optimized application performance (CPU, memory, loadings)

### Unreal Engine Programmer - Survive the Fall, Angry Bulls Studio

OCTOBER 2021 - FEBRUARY 2022

Small part-time order at the early stage of Survive the Fall development.

Worked on core system for setting up gameplay by designers and RTS controls.

### **Unity Programmer - Tower of Time, Event Horizon**

MAY 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2018

#### PC Release in 04/2018

https://store.steampowered.com/app/617480/Tower\_of\_Time/

Tower of Time was first project in game dev I've worked on in newly emerging game studio Event Horizon. During that time I was still studying on University so it was part-time job mostly. I was chiefly responsible for gameplay programming and tools in small team of 4 programmers. I led development of exploration & quest features and mentored content creators.

# **Education**

Bachelors Degree in Computer Science, Gdańsk University of Technology

OCTOBER 2014 - FEBRUARY 2018